**Using shareholder rights and collaborative activism**, we seek to drive the urgent adoption of strategies and targets which deliver climate outcomes aligned with the goals of the Paris Agreement, and to advocate for change in the private sector to reduce inequality.

    **We exercise the rights and powers of shareholders**, using research, advocacy and activism, to advance social and environmental justice.
    
    Climate Change
    --------------

    Inequality
    ----------

    **Explore our publications**

    “**A just transition for all towards an environmentally sustainable economy**, needs to be well managed and contribute to the goals of decent work for all, social inclusion and the eradication of poverty.” International Labour Organisation, 2015

Search  Search

Privacy policy
==============

Your privacy is critically important to us.

Just Share is located at:  Aintree Business Park, Block C, Unit FB, Doncaster Rd & Loch Rd, Kenilworth, Cape Town, 7708.

This privacy policy applies to [https://justshare.org.za](https://justshare.org.za/) (“the Website”). Just Share respects your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating the Website, and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the website. We have adopted this privacy policy to explain what information may be collected on the Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This privacy policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.

This privacy policy, together with the [terms & conditions](https://justshare.org.za/terms-conditions) posted on the Website, set out the general rules and policies governing your use of the website. Depending on your activities when visiting the Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.

Website visitors
----------------

Like most website operators, Just Share collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visit or request. Just Share’s purpose in collecting non-personally-identifying information is to better understand how Just Share’s visitors use the Website. From time to time, Just Share may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate.

Gathering of personally-identifying information
-----------------------------------------------

Certain visitors to the Website choose to interact with Just Share in ways that require Just Share to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Just Share gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up to our mailing list at [https://justshare.org.za](https://justshare.org.za/) to provide their name and email address.

Security
--------

The security of your personal information is important to us. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security, given that no method of transmission over the internet, nor of electronic storage, is completely secure.

Links to external sites
-----------------------

The Website may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s website. We strongly advise you to review the privacy policy and terms and conditions of every site you visit. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, products or services.

Aggregated statistics
---------------------

Just Share may collect statistics about the behaviour of visitors to the Website. Just Share may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Just Share will not disclose your personally-identifying information.

Cookies
-------

To enrich your online experience, Just Share uses “cookies”, similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalised content, appropriate advertising and to store your preferences on your computer.

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Just Share uses cookies to help us identify and track visitors, their usage of the Website, and their website access preferences. Just Share visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using the Just Share website, with the drawback that certain features of the Website may not function properly without cookies.

By continuing to navigate the Website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to Just Share’s use of cookies.

Privacy policy changes
----------------------

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Just Share may change its privacy policy from time to time, and in Just Share’s sole discretion. Just Share encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its privacy policy. Your continued use of the Website after any change in this privacy policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

Contact us
----------

**General enquiries**  

**Media enquiries**  

Just Share NPC, Unit B01, Plum Park,  
25 Gabriel Road, Plumstead, Cape Town 7800

About
-----

Stay up to date
---------------

Join our mailing list for the latest Just Share news

     Please leave this field empty

Email Address \*

First Name \*

Last Name \*

 I have read and agree to the [Privacy Policy](https://justshare.org.za/privacy-policy) and [Terms & Conditions](https://justshare.org.za/terms-conditions)

Please check your inbox or spam folder to confirm your subscription.

Copyright 2024 Just Share. All rights reserved.

Make a donation
---------------

Our work is only possible with the generous support of philanthropic funding and individual donations, which are tax deductible.

Every contribution helps us to keep doing what we do. Please consider making a donation and becoming part of the movement working to build a more just, equal and sustainable country.

Please email us at [donate@justshare.org.za](mailto:donate@justshare.org.za) to request a section 18A Tax Certificate.

| Donate via EFT | Below are our bank details |
| --- | --- |
| Bank | Nedbank |
| Account number | 1172492603 |
| Account type | Business PAYU |
| Branch code | 10134000 |
| Branch name | CPT Western Suburbs Metro BB |

Scan the QR code below in your SnapScan mobile app to complete the payment
